{
    "subject": "resource/WHKY-TV",
    "predicate": "property/subchannels",
    "object": "14.5",
    "human_readable": "WHKY-TV has a subchannel of 14.5.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8754072189331055,
            "question": "Does WHKY-TV have a subchannel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7903416752815247,
            "question": "What is the subchannel number of WHKY-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7785156965255737,
            "question": "Which number identifies a subchannel on WHKY-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7780887484550476,
            "question": "WHKY-TV broadcasts on which subchannel number?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7116653919219971,
            "question": "What is the numerical designation of WHKY-TV's subchannel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7090898156166077,
            "question": "How can viewers access the subchannel of WHKY-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7071636915206909,
            "question": "WHKY-TV's subchannel number is...?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6975615620613098,
            "question": "What programming might be found on WHKY-TV's subchannel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6645275950431824,
            "question": "Is there a specific channel designated for additional content on WHKY-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4853333830833435,
            "question": "Besides its main channel, what additional channel does WHKY-TV offer?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=WHKY-TV has a subchannel of 14.5.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5119_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a specific channel designated for additional content on WHKY-TV?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5119_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What programming might be found on WHKY-TV's subchannel?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5119_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=WHKY-TV's subchannel number is...?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5119_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5119_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5119_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5119_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5119_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5119_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5119_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5119_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5119_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5119_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5119_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text excerpts do not mention any information about WHKY-TV having a subchannel of 14.5.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information suggesting that WHKY-TV has a subchannel of 14.5. The relevant passage states that \"WHKY-TV, virtual channel 14 (UHF digital channel 40),\" but it does not mention a subchannel of 14.5."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}